This program is brought to you by the
members of the special team.
We will raise the excitement level in
the world!
Mayumi wins!
Thank you.
Mayumi's turn.
I'll do my best.
I always think about the future.
I can't do anything.
She's so cool.
Thank you.
If you win, you can get a free drink
for 1,200 yen.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
Did you know about this club?
The van in front of the classroom is
cute, isn't it?
How did you know?
Did you know a long time ago?
I know my friend your first name is
Meju.
Ignore.
We are half-married.
Ah, sure.
I'm also an adolescent of Melon.
Thank you for watching.
He's a busybody.
See you soon in the Far East!
Anne, vocal training seminar!
Please support us!
Ah, yes, I see.
I see.
We are your Happy Team, Rokkyo!
We are Chou!
But, but, but, don't be afraid
You can run away, you can run away
The game has begun
And it's not the end yet
Yes, yes.
The sun is disappearing into the crowd
It's the worst to look down from the
side
Is it too late now?
July
I have to stop, I have to stop
Love Potion
You are love, right?
Love Love Love
OK
Let's run
I can't stop, I can't stop, I can't
stop
I'm noticing love
Love Potion
I can't leave you alone
1, 2, 3, 4
Go Go Tomorrow
Forever Tomorrow
The best
Go Go Tomorrow
Forever Tomorrow
The best
Go Go Tomorrow
Even if it's just one day
The worst
Good job
Tomorrow will be a better day
Thank you
Please check
Please collaborate with Annie
And be with us again
Thank you
2 days before the actual live
performance
Yes.
How was it?
It was good.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Thank you very much.
It was so wide.
The first floor was so wide.
I'm watching you.
Today is lunch time.
We are going to have an opening
performance.
I'm so nervous.
Are you OK?
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous, too.
I borrowed Toki-sen-chan's costume.
I don't know if I can wear it in the
morning, so I tried it on.
It was totally different from what
Toki-sen-chan wore.
I can't wear it.
Are you OK?
I'm not wearing it.
I'm wearing pink.
Right.
I'm always wearing purple.
I was wondering about that costume.
When everyone was wearing purple.
When we were in the arena.
It's a cute costume.
I'm looking forward to it.
We'll do our best.
5,000 yen.
5,000 yen?
Yes.
Thank you.
Next, Hiori, Julia, and...
Julia will be with Rin-chan, and we'll
have a dance time.
We'll do a rehearsal.
We'll start the rehearsal.
Thank you.
I'm wearing the costume of Haru.
I was told that I was going to wear the
costume of Hitomi, but I said thank you.
We are TimeTimes.
Thank you.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I've come to like you
The popular feeling, love, will
eventually turn into love
It's complicated, but it's simple
I love you
Da Da Da Da Da Da Da Da Da
Good morning from Hajima A. Yea,
happiness every time
Thank you very much.
Wow!
It's super rare.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to react seriously.
Wow!
I'm so excited.
It's so cute.
I'm so nervous.
Everyone is watching.
Thank you.
It's so good.
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to our channel.
Golden Punch! Golden Punch!
The white curtain will be blown.
You will fall down.
Please pretend to be strong.
Put your hands on your hair.
You should be close to the white
curtain.
You should be close to it.
You can't do it.
You can do it!
Thank you for your cooperation today.
Thank you.
I was happy to see that everyone was
practicing a lot and it was cute.
I hope you enjoy the fans who are
watching with a lot of smiles.
Thank you for your cooperation today.
Thank you to the staff.
Thank you.
The bento is luxurious.
It looks delicious.
Shabu-shabu. It's healthy.
Happy New Year!
Thank you.
I'm going to put it in the mirror.
I chose the Salaspa steak from Abeli
Wagyu.
The meat is...
Oh, it's the same steak.
The same steak.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Awkward
Today, the opening actors Juria and
Rina
will perform during lunch break.
It's judgement-based on which singer
will sing the song.
Ayaka wants to do a great example.
strawberries
You look beautiful!
Fumiko, you look great!
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
It suits you.
Cute.
Stop it.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm nervous.
Santa never give up.
If you're done, you can go change.
Thank you.
I'm off!
Bye bye!
I'm so nervous!
Skip skip skip...
Oh! It's Haruka!
Hi!
I'm also Haruka.
Hey! It's Haruka!
I never said that!
Welcome to my room.
I'm Haruka Koyuzumi.
Hmm…
I'm the leader of NANCHI TIME, Hiyori-
chan.
Why?
This is my first time hearing that.
I'm the leader of NANCHI TIME.
Oh, really?
Then I'll be the leader.
I'm NANCHI TIME's Yoshikawa Hiyori.
Instagram name is NEEEEGUMI
I will say my name and say ROCK ON!
Let's go with that
Lunch time?
Yes!
ROCK ON!
Shall we do ROCK ON CHEAT?
Let's do it
Before the show
Before the show?
Now?
Anyway
Let's start with the leader.
Hiyori, Julia, Nene, Lunch Time, Rock
On!
Applause!
Let's do our best!
Please!
I'm nervous.
Don't talk!
WHats the situation now side back?
I'm a clever girl.
Can people see it already?
The fog took a lot.
I'm worried that those people see.
Please stand up.
Let's go.
Let's go to the stage.
Thank you.
adequate Sailor Snow
Tadan!
Its Ranr же
that's 살살 disagreement
Is the sal Kazuya
boy
yeah, I was Goma
well Kougeban
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'll give the final egg to my sisterα
to celebrate.
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'm getting closer from behind
I'm going to hit the back of the wall
Believe in love
I know, but I'm a little dizzy
Sometimes I write a letter
Promise me your true love
Forever by my side
I'm sure it's okay
I'm living for you
I'm sorry, I'm not saying anything
I really don't like this
I don't want to hear it
I don't want to hear this feeling
Please subscribe to our channel!
I'm going to take a picture!
A picture? A video?
A video!
It's cute!
Next is...
I'm going to take a picture!
I'll be back!
Bye bye!
Everyone is dancing.
Cute.
oberoi
Best friends, Mirai priorities.
This song's 위향님, 그대encie 김홍비 와 her
name.
Which box was it?
Amazing!
I can hear different kinds of sound
here!
♪Anime, Nane Negai socью baba!
Wonderful!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
I was so scared!
Thank you for the prize!
It was fun!
It looked like fun!
When we were skiing, everyone was
holding the camera
and I was like, oh yeah, we're going to
be filmed!
It was so much fun!
It was so cute!
We danced hoping that we would get more
fans,
and we should have gotten more fans!
It was fun.
I'm looking forward to it.
Congratulations.
Thank you for watching.
I don't know what to say next.
I have to hurry up.
Next, the super-exciting voice actors!
Thank you!
Let's have fun with everyone here and
everyone watching the live broadcast!
On Paribaru 2021 Start!
The opening has ended!
We are now at lunchtime!
It's our first lunchtime show!
Oh, wait, wait.
Let's start with Reni-chan.
Sorry, let's start with Reni-chan.
It was our first time to be in a group
other than Momokuro.
And we were able to do a pose for
lunchtime.
We were also able to be appointed as
the leader of Hiori.
It's been a while since we did that.
I really love Toki-chan.
I'm so happy that my dream came true.
I wonder if I can be with Reni-chan.
When I watch the rehearsal video with
Reni-chan at home,
I feel like, oh, it's Reni-chan.
It's a strange feeling.
I'm so happy that it's amazing.
I'm so happy that I can be with her.
I want to say that.
I saw the rehearsal video, and I was
surprised at the two of us.
I can't remember my position at all.
If I say this, my teacher will get
angry.
I don't remember at all.
I think I have to remember, but I'm
going to be with her.
I was so happy.
I'm so happy.
Everyone is so excited.
We can shoot when we want.
Everyone is holding the camera.
Please spread the word about us.
Thank you.
I borrowed the costume for this
shooting.
Thank you, Haru-chan.
Thank you, too.
You said, I borrowed the costume for
this shooting.
Thank you so much.
I couldn't choose the costume for the
song.
I was asked what kind of costume I
should wear.
And I found Hishin-chan's costume was
so cute.
I'm a big fan of her.
I wanted to wear this costume.
I thought I couldn't wear this costume.
I was so nervous.
I'm a big fan of Haru-chan.
I think I've proven that Tokisen-chan
is cute.
I'm so happy.
We're happy, too.
I'm really selfish in this way, but I
want to do more in lunch time.
I want to collaborate with Tokisen-
chan.
I want to collaborate with everyone.
Please, adults.
We're going to prepare for it soon.
I'll help you with anything.
I like YouTube, so I want to do a
commercial with Aki-chan.
I like the commercial for goods.
I'm so happy.
It's a heart-to-heart series.
I hope we can get along well.
I'm so happy.
Thank you for coming.
I'm a commentator.
I'm going to eat this.
It looks delicious.
It looks really good.
It's cute.
Look at this.
My pinky is standing.
It's standing.
It's been standing for a long time.
How is it?
It's good.
Is it good?
I can't say anything but it's good.
I'm so excited.
It's really good.
It's so fun, isn't it?
It's so fun!
It's so short!
It is not like you're a big boss right?
That is sort of like...
Because that monokuma who buried on the
floor
Oh so you're like this
Despite everyone's disagreement
An unaaaable
Here we go!
So, we are starting Hayakamibara 2020
now.
Good job, Julia!
Thank you!
Lunch time!
We will take a break and do the opening
act.
We will have our performance soon.
Yes!
We are so grateful.
We have been working for 30 minutes.
We will perform with ARIN.
Are you happy?
When we performed the opening act,
we were so happy to have a lot of fans.
We are so happy.
Thank you!
I can say this because it will be
announced.
I don't know what kind of clothes ARIN
will wear at this stage.
I don't know.
I'm looking forward to it.
We prepared a lot of shoes.
The design is different.
We have almost the same shoes.
I'm not complaining.
We have a few types, but we haven't
decided which one to wear.
I want to wear more shoes.
It's easy to take pictures if you wear
them.
So, I'll leave them.
I'm looking forward to seeing what ARIN
will wear.
We will choose cute and fluttering
clothes for the rehearsal.
I'm looking forward to seeing what it
will be like.
We'll do our best!
We're going to perform at the Tokyo
Dome!
I'm so excited!
We've been waiting for this moment for
25 minutes.
I'm so excited.
We've been waiting for this moment for
25 minutes.
We've been saying that we want to
perform at the Tokyo Dome.
But we've never performed at the Tokyo
Dome.
We'll show you how great the Budokan
is.
We'll do our best to show you our
performance.
We'll make this place a promotional
venue.
We'll do it!
We were a bit nervous during the
rehearsal.
We did it!
We're aiming for this place.
We'll do our best to get closer to the
Tokyo Dome.
There are many people wearing T-shirts.
Thank you.
Let's enjoy it!
It's starting!
Let's go!
I'm having fun.
Size changes to increase speed
Is it serious?
2 o'clock
This is normal
The last
The sis we noticed
Thanks for watching!
Shine
Yeah
Come on
One more time
One, two ~!
stage
The final stop
Thank you for watching.
The hair has started to fall down.
Everyone is completely amino acid.
Mukai-san decided to sleep in one car
at the gospel house.
We'll keep filming CDs of festivals.
All together now!!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Together forever!!
Thank you for watching!
Mission No.1
A little rusty street light
The heart's heartbeat when we meet
I can't hear your voice, right?
Ah...
Next year's town
I won't let go of your hand
Is it too late to say goodbye?
In July, I'll spend time with you
I'm still, still, still not ready
Please tell me
I'm still in love with you
I feel like I can be confident
Because I want to like you
I want to be able to feel that feeling
I would like to sing together with
someone
Ready?
A-mi
Wow!
I love you!
I'll wear it!
So cute!
I've been wearing the same one as
everyone.
Thank you!
So cute!
I've chosen the shortest skirt among
all the clothes I have.
Thank you!
Because everyone's skirts are short.
I'm so happy!
But I'm not that old, so I'm not that
hungry.
I've been trying to fit everyone's
size.
I'll keep running, even if my strings
come undone
My heart is pounding
Did you all get a rock on from us?
Thank you very much!
We'll be back at the Budokan as a super
special event, so please wait for us!
Well then,
Rock on to your heart!
This has been Super Doki Doki Channel!
Thank you very much!
It was so fun!
It's hot!
My hair is all messy!
I have a lot of hair on my head!
It's so cute!
My butt is shaking!
Next is...
We will sing the song of Komokoro-san
with the audience.
We will sing the song of Gorilla Punch.
Hyurin will play the role of Gorilla,
so please look forward to it.
I heard the song of Gorilla Punch.
Who is Gorilla?
Gorilla-san.
Yes.
Boss Gorilla.
I'm a panda.
I'm a gorilla with a sharp tail.
The first cut is amazing.
It's cool.
I'll do my best.
I'm a gorilla with a sharp tail.
Please look forward to the next
episode.
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
What's your order?
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
We're the Gattens!
Today's a bright day again
We're running around and having fun
Sparkling dreams and pins
We're dancing in the sun
We're having fun
Yay!
Playing with Orin like a gorilla
What is going on?
I am losing confidence here.
Support for Shizuya Island
I can't wash this.
I'm so high, leave it to me!
Let's go!
So,
Ta-da!
We changed into our 2021 T-shirts!
Yay!
So cute!
Can you see the back?
Each of us has our name on it.
Oh, there's Juri.
Where's Akita?
Oh, there's Hiyori.
Everyone's name is on it.
Oh, Konomi.
The name is on the front.
but it should be okay.
Communicating period
textured
Meca
It is a circuit that allows momentum.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching!
Everyone in Japan! Thank you!
It was amazing!
I'm so happy!
What color is your hair now?
Black.
No, it's not.
It's a little bit black.
It's me.
Oh, it's you.
The color of the mask.
Oh, that's cute.
It's black.
It's cute.
It's a T-shirt.
It's a cute T-shirt.
It has your name on it.
It has our names on it.
I'm happy.
I think so, too.
We sang the opening song together, and
we danced to the chorus of the song.
We danced for 25 minutes at the live
party. We had a lot of fun.
It was a great memory.
It was fun.
We danced to 7 people's songs.
We danced to the opening song of JILLA
& KUU's song.
We danced a lot.
We danced to the song of ENJIN channel.
Kiyori was the leader.
Shuri was the leader of LUNCHTIME.
LUNCHTIME Rock'n'Roll!
We are a group with a long history.
We just started to work.
The leader is the national treasure.
I got a letter from RENI saying that I
want to do it again.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want to collaborate with RENI.
I want to do it. I want to appear in a
goods commercial.
I want to do it with AKIRA.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's do it.
Please.
I'm glad to have a senior like you.
I'm glad to have a chance to
collaborate with other idols.
Let's aim for it.
Let's do our best.
Thank you for coming to Ayaka.
Thank you for watching.
Bye bye.
The world is shining
I can be relaxed by turning the
umbrella
If not, I can't walk
Surely, someone is crying somewhere
I'll get wet somewhere again
It's not cold
Surely, someone is crying somewhere
I want to share my feelings with you
The scenery that I don't know is still
in front of me
Let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
It's a city after the rain
I'll draw a fragment of the future on
the canvas of my damaged heart
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I play the piano of the rainbow
with the sound of the rainbow
Goodbye, goodbye
to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a flower
I shed tears
I wear a rainbow dress